newsden.net 2018-01-06

# Privacy Policy - NewsDen

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is very important to us. To ensure we protect your privacy we give this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page of our site where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting NewsDen.net, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Basic visitor information used to map trends of visitor numbers and geographic locations may be passed to third party advertisers when appraising advertising rates. No personal information such as names, addresses, email addresses, IP addresses will be passed on to any third parties.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
At times we may serve advertisements through Google Adsense as a third party advertisement vendor who uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of NewsDen.net then you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> .
